<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fashion on Philip Mitroi</title>
    <link>http://philipmitroi.github.io/tags/fashion/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fashion on Philip Mitroi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy;2017 Philip Mitroi</copyright>
    <atom:link href="http://philipmitroi.github.io/tags/fashion/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Stas</title>
      <link>http://philipmitroi.github.io/portfolio/stas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://philipmitroi.github.io/portfolio/stas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A session with my friend Stas
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://philipmitroi.github.io/img/portfolio/work1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Stas1&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stas is one of my closest friends, he&amp;rsquo;s an emerging artist from Toronto who you can find on soundcloud under the moniker Yani. I think he and I go for a shoot at least once every week. On top of taking pictures for him, I also produce a great deal of music for him. In these industries I find it very important to have someone around who you can work with on anything, messages may be lost in translation should the aesthetic or message be limited to a single format. By allowing me to work with him on both visual and acoustic platforms, we achieve a unique aesthetic that is consistent all across the board of his brand, with more control than assembling content from sources produced by different people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;soundcloud.com/babyboiyani&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out some more photos from the session below:
&lt;img src=&#34;http://philipmitroi.github.io/img/portfolio/stas2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Stas2&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://philipmitroi.github.io/img/portfolio/stas3.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Stas3&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Selection from a retail catalog</title>
      <link>http://philipmitroi.github.io/portfolio/catal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 19:44:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://philipmitroi.github.io/portfolio/catal/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A collection of images that were used for advertising and promo for my friend&amp;rsquo;s retail business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naturally, one of the first people I shot with was Stas. You can see other projects I&amp;rsquo;ve done with him on the website&amp;rsquo;s homepage, just look for his image!
In a more corporate setting, you would probably find a team of people working on this project. Beyond the photographer, there would probably be a stylist and a team for hair/makeup, as well as someone to act as the project&amp;rsquo;s creative director. Luckily for us, Stas already has an affinity for luxury fashion and portraying it in a way that would make it appealing. As a person who is also interested in some of the brands that the store offers (Rick Owens, Supreme, Bape, etc), doing this project was a blast.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out some of the images below:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://philipmitroi.github.io/img/portfolio/3/rick.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;trickyricky&#34; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;http://philipmitroi.github.io/img/portfolio/3/1001.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;bag1&#34; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;http://philipmitroi.github.io/img/portfolio/3/bag2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;bag2&#34; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;http://philipmitroi.github.io/img/portfolio/3/seated.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;seated&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>